
export const quizQuestions_2 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does JSX stand for?',
      choices: ['JavaScript XML', 'Java Syntax Extension', 'JSON XML', 'JavaScript Extension'],
      correctAnswer: 'JavaScript XML',
    },
    {
      question: 'In React, what is JSX used for?',
      choices: ['Defining styles', 'Defining components', 'Managing state', 'Handling events'],
      correctAnswer: 'Defining components',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you write comments in JSX?',
      choices: ['// This is a comment', '{/* This is a comment */}', '<!-- This is a comment -->', '/** This is a comment */'],
      correctAnswer: '{/* This is a comment */}',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is a valid JSX expression?',
      choices: ['<div>', '{var x = 5;}', 'if (x === 5) {<p>Hello</p>}', '<p className="red-text">Hello</p>'],
      correctAnswer: '<p className="red-text">Hello</p>',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of Babel in a React project?',
      choices: ['Managing state', 'Transpiling JSX to JavaScript', 'Routing in React', 'Handling events'],
      correctAnswer: 'Transpiling JSX to JavaScript',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can you embed JavaScript expressions in JSX?',
      choices: ['<% expression %>', '{ expression }', '{{ expression }}', '<# expression #>'],
      correctAnswer: '{ expression }',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is the correct way to render a component in JSX?',
      choices: ['{<MyComponent />}', '<render MyComponent />', '<MyComponent.render />', '<MyComponent />'],
      correctAnswer: '<MyComponent />',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the role of the ReactDOM library in a React application?',
      choices: ['Managing state', 'Handling events', 'Rendering React components in the DOM', 'Routing in React'],
      correctAnswer: 'Rendering React components in the DOM',
    },
    {
      question: 'In JSX, how can you create a self-closing tag?',
      choices: ['<selfClosing>', '<selfClosing />', '<selfClosing></selfClosing>', '<selfClosing/>'],
      correctAnswer: '<selfClosing />',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is NOT a valid JSX attribute?',
      choices: ['className', 'class', 'onClick', 'value'],
      correctAnswer: 'class',
    },
  ],
}